Yes, yes, we have brought a video which will tell you about some
situations,
after some time, that
we are interested in travel insurance, then
somewhere else,
perhaps no one has heard about travelling, travelling on
travelling, it is not necessary that you
travel internationally,
how many people are coming and going, that there is hatred from breaking,
subscribing,
going by train, car, taxi are being hired, then in
any way, it is
necessary to have travel insurance, it is
not necessary that you do not travel like this, you will have to move
quickly, then how much
a deserted place, as much as a normal protein, let's go, that a little will do,
reply to the picture, your net will also do,
that is the last, no matter how much booking is done, we
book a train, we are our
Punjabi people, no matter how much journey we go on, we would sacrifice our lives, that
this will also be done,
in our cities Haryana comes,
from our cities also Harmandar Sahib will go, if the
family goes to Patna, then they might not
know, information has been given by vandalizing, knowledge
in Hindi, many very much train, the
insurance beautiful travel  I am insurance,
that is only and only their oath taking horoscope,
money, money, money, travelling with others like this, a
lot of 10 lakhs, leaving aside 10 minutes, means that up
to 10 lakhs, money is not taken, the
dead gorgeous of the competitions, he can get up
to 10 lakhs during train journey, so leaving aside that also,
many types of issues have raised one's insurance decision,
when the train was taking this bag, these
documents should be there, if you are
sick or not, then
you should
definitely say that travelling should be done, I have started doing
some
travel insurance companies,
Punjabi and
Tata company
also does hatred, secondly this trend is 49 paise,
so we have
found your account in our India, then your respect was
saved, the passbook of those who got the Malwa airport, we
said till Delhi airport, then we gave it till
Amritsar, Jalandhar, the criminals buses
run, be it Indo-Canadian or Tibet, you
must do travel insurance, that when
Haryana, Punjab and then we were not very expensive,
their picture was born or born in Punjab, then it was
not a matter, that death
claim bag was worn on the back of the neck  You have so many daily
airplane related issues that have come out from their place,
they get flights to Argentina
from there, this tap, a little help
for quick related matters, today I have done Jizya
International Travel Vehicle, if I have to
travel to any country,
it is absolutely necessary in today's time
because it is quality time, there is
time so that travel insurance is
mandatory, I have
booked the tickets of the councilors, at that
time I am a part of the pictures related
website, I have booked the tickets, that
sarees website has been appointed, if the
enemies will be
travel insurance Radhakishan, then there was
no money, then the stairs website is that
irregular
sexual ropes or policy market, this,
which after a day I face them and
find the age account, this daughter of mine is 25
years old, Vijay Pandit traveled for half the day to
Dubai, more travel was to Dubai, I have to give
₹400 ₹500 to everything,
normal people should
meet on the issue of Punjabi four days,
a doctor and a doctor's
scientist, age, da and  Company's
account we are kind enough to consider $15,000 the sum
assured napkin or $36,000 the same
leave inside with a jade flour we checked for a
little while first of all find out your
age date of birth etc something in the world
now this middle up to one lakh dollars 10 we should see a bag a
little gomez guruji
pack place the claim is filed no
passport is lost that claim
punch some
small still helped so
jury can be
completed that
I will have
my behavior enter loot during travel you will
get spoil for free
check before hospital and bell travel god's it is
absolutely free there will be no problem
then if you liked a little information then
travel insurance itself that is it is
not necessary to have any subject water or
any online computer
knowledge ghr ghr
[Music]
in description
subscribe mobile numbers if you liked the
information then
subscribe and share the channel
information so that you can also know what is happening travel
insurance 12 according to many  If there is
no insurance, tell me too, you people
Punjabi Adab Pendil Haq Yadav, let's say I am sick, I have
coriander insurance, I have
life insurance, but I
cannot leave it on medical grounds, Anna, after telling him this life
insurance, after a lot of persuasion,
Noorjahan, being a wife, should leave the vitamins, it is
good, especially the important day
prevents the international from getting the gems, he has gone to Patna Sahib, he will also roam around, he will go to
Harmandir Sahib, we are here,
Gurudwara Sahib, no matter how many times it will go, he is going by
train, we have our
family, let's go, we are in a hurry, but we did
not inform anyone that they arranged for the travelling, so
I should stay by train, the
Punjab money was one, please like and due to the environment,
Sonu came, he had
played in the Ramdasi's fetus two years ago, money should go
here, go to 66, there may be some
ups and downs or there may be regret of the Lord,
please share this information more, if you get
30 chakli in the video, then like, share, subscribe,
please support,
Bluetooth, some support day and channel, Vadhu's
Tapa and video, Pranam Dada, I feel like it  If you
subscribe fresh then it is a very good
call Chalna Talwar ji